https://parameter.io/privacy-policy/

What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://parameter.io/terms-conditionsYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.GDPR ComplianceTo comply with the new GDPR laws for users in the European Economic Area (EEA) we have made some changes to our website.You will now be prompted whether you wish to retain your email and name when commenting, if you choose yes, a cookie will be stored on your computer to identify yourself next time you comment.  If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.Blockonomi may process your Personal Data because:We need to perform a contract with youYou have given us permission to do soThe processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rightsFor payment processing purposesTo comply with the lawData Protection Rights (GDPR)If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Blockonomi aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Niche Site Project relied on your consent to process your personal information.Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.25th May 2018: GDPR Compliance AddedContacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Parameter Kooc Media Ltd. International House, 61 Mosley Street, Manchester, M2 3HZ UK hello@kooc.co.uk
Search for:
Latest Posts 10 Best HOTAS Joysticks: Complete Buyer’s Guide 12 Best Nerf Guns: The Complete Buyer’s Guide for All Budgets 10 Best Emergency Radios: Complete Buyer’s Guide 10 Best Telescopes for Kids: Ultimate Buyer’s Guide Best Laptop Cooling Pads: Complete Buyer’s GuideCategoriesCryptocurrencyDesignGamingHardwareNewsPhotographyPress ReleaseReviewsSoftwareTechnologyToysWeb DevelopmentOur SitesBlockonomiCircloMoneyCheckAlienWPBeanstalkBe Active OutdoorsGardenBeastHomesOutlineVinjatekTodaysCacherAboutParameter is a blog about Technology, Cryptocurrency, Gaming and Software.Our WordPress Hosting is Provided by WPEngine.
Submit Type above and press Enter to search. Press Esc to cancel.
